Guide to the Salwa Mikdadi Papers AD.MC.022
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Artists files (individual), 1960-2005, and undated; 1989-1994; 12.5 Linear Feet in 30 boxes.
  - Shishiny, Naima el-
    - Shishiny, Naima el-: Visuals, 1980-1989, and undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Shoman, Suha-Hilmi
    - Shoman, Suha-Hilmi: Biographical, 1988-1998 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Shoman, Suha-Hilmi: Correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Shoman, Suha-Hilmi: Visuals, 1989-2004, and undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Shoukairy, Rula el-
    - Shoukairy, Rula el-: Biographical and correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Shoukairy, Rula el-: Visuals, 1996 and undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Sinno, Nuha
    - Sinno, Nuha, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Sinnokrot, Nida
    - Sinnokrot, Nida, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Sirry, Gazbia
    - Sirry, Gazbia: Biographical, 1990-2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Sirry, Gazbia: Correspondence, 1992-2003 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Sirry, Gazbia: Visuals, 1990-1993, and undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Soubra, Oumaya
    - Soubra, Oumaya: biographical, 1993 and undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Soubra, Oumaya: correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Soubra, Oumaya: visuals, 1992 and undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Soumi, Nasser
    - Soumi, Nasser, 1989-1992, and undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Sukkarieh, Rabia
    - Sukkarieh, Rabia: biographical, 1992 and undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Sukkarieh, Rabia: correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Sukkarieh, Rabia: visuals, 1989-1995 and undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Sununu, Clara
    - Sununu, Clara, 1992 and undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Sweifi, Mervat el-
    - Sweifi, Mervat el-, 1989-1993, and undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Tabbaa, Dodi
    - Tabbaa, Dodi, 1990-1996 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Tabbaa, Samer
    - Tabbaa, Samer, 1980-1996 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Tallal, Chaibia
    - Tallal, Chaibia: biographical, 1985-1993 and undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Tallal, Chaibia: correspondence, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Tallal, Chaibia: visuals, 1982 and undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Tamari, Vera
    - Tamari, Vera: biographical, 1991 and undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Tamari, Vera: correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Tamari, Vera: visuals, 1990 and undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Tamari, Vladimir
    - Tamari, Vladimir: biographical and correspondence, 1982-1999 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Tamari, Vladimir: visuals, 1988-1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Tarazi, Solange
    - Tarazi, Solange: biographical and correspondence, 1983-1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Tarazi, Solange: visuals, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Terlizzi, Judith
    - Terlizzi, Judith, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Ternar, Mine
    - Ternar, Mine: biographical, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Ternar, Mine: visuals, 1990-1995 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Tijani, Latifa al
    - Tijani, Latifa al, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Toubasi, Faten
    - Toubasi, Faten, 1986-1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Tuma, Mary Bahjah
    - Tuma, Mary Bahjah: biographical, 2000-2003 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Tuma, Mary Bahjah: correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Tuma, Mary Bahjah: visuals, 1993-2003 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Umar, Madiha
    - Umar, Madiha: biographical, 1981-2005 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Umar, Madiha: correspondence, 1992-2005 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Umar, Madiha: visuals, 1947-1992 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Unknown
    - Unknown, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Wardi, Hanaa al-
    - Wardi, Hanaa al-: biographical and correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Wardi, Hanaa al-: visuals, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Yacoubian, Violette
    - Yacoubian, Violette, 1982-1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Yesilnil, Aysegul
    - Yesilnil, Aysegul: biographical and correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Yesilnil, Aysegul: visuals, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Zacharia, Nasri
    - Zacharia, Nasri, 1992-1998 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Zakariya, Mohamed
    - Zakariya, Mohamed: biographical and correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Zakariya, Mohamed: visuals, undated (pre-1990) (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Zarou, Salwa
    - Zarou, Salwa, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Zaru, Samia
    - Zaru, Samia: biographical, 1989-1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Zaru, Samia: correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Zaru, Samia: visuals, 1982-1991 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Zayat, Elias
    - Zayat, Elias, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Zeid, Fahrelnissa
    - Zeid, Fahrelnissa: biographical and correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Zeid, Fahrelnissa: visuals, undated (1964-1965) (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Zghal, Emna
    - Zghal, Emna: biographical and correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Zghal, Emna: visuals, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Zibawi, Mahmoud
    - Zibawi, Mahmoud, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Zineb, Sedira
    - Zineb, Sedira: biographical, 1997-2004 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Zineb, Sedira: visuals, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Ziyeh, Samiramis
    - Ziyeh, Samiramis: biographical, 1994-1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Ziyeh, Samiramis: correspondence, 1994-1998 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Ziyeh, Samiramis: visuals, 1994-1998 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Zughaib, Helen
    - Zughaib, Helen: biographical, 1997-2004 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Zughaib, Helen: correspondence, 1989-2005 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Zughaib, Helen: visuals, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Zurayk, Afaf
    - Zurayk, Afaf: biographical, 1980-1997 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Zurayk, Afaf: correspondence, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Zurayk, Afaf: visuals, 1990-2004 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Artists: Country: Egypt, 1986-1994 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Artists: Country: Egypt, 1995-1999 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Artists, country: Egypt, 2000-2004 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Artists, country: Egypt, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Artists, country: Gulf states (Bahrain, Kuwait, Qatar), 1988-2006 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Artists, country: Iraq, 1985-1994, and undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Artists, country: Iraq, 1995-2007 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Artists, country: Israel, 1997-2004 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Artists, country: Jordan, 1996-2003, and undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Artists, country: Lebanon, 1979-1993 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Artists, country: Lebanon, 1994-1996 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Artists, country: Lebanon, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Artists, country: Lebanon, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Artists, country: Lebanon, 1999-2005 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Artists, country: Lebanon, miscellaneous, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Artists, country: Lebanon, news clippings, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Artists, country: Morocco, 1989-2001 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Artists, country: Palestine, 1990-2006 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Artists, country: Palestine: Union of Palestinian Artists, 1988 and undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Artists, country: Saudi Arabia, 1994-2004 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Artists, country: Sudan, 1991-1999 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Artists, country: Syria, 1979-2001 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Artists, country: Syria: Galerie Atassi, Damascus, 1994-1997 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Artists, country: Tunisia, 1998-2002 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Artists, country: various, 1988-2004 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Artists, country: various: silk painters, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Tobia, Noha, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- ICWA records, 1987-2007; 2.5 Linear Feet in 6 boxes.
  - Administrative, 1992-1999
    - Artists, lists of (databases), 1992-1996, and undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, office, 1994-1996, and undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Forms: artist's consent and others, 1992-1999, and undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters and brochures, 1993-1997 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Promotional materials (brochures and greeting cards), 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Public relations, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1992-1999 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Staffing, 1992-1997 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1987-2002
    - Afkhani, Mahnaz, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Ameen, Souad (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Art organizations and galleries, 1988-1996 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Artists, various, 1995-2004 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - California, 1992-1994 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Colleges and universities, 1992-2002 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Countries: Algeria, 1993-1995 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Countries: Egypt, 1991-1995 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Countries: Jordan, 1993-1995 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Countries: Kuwait, 1990-1994 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Countries: Lebanon, 1989-1996 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Countries: Morocco, 1989-1999 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Countries: Saudi Arabia, 1992-1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Countries: Syria, 1992-1998 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Countries: Tunisia, 1989-1996 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Countries: United Arab Emirates, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Countries: Yemen, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Cultural Foundation, United Arab Emirates, 1992-1994 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising (charitable foundations), 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - General, 1987-1993 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - General, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - General, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - General, 1996-2001 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Hijab, Nadia, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Honorary board, 1991-1993 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Institut du Monde Arabe (Paris), 1991-1995 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - L'Atelier / Galerie d'Art Moderne (Rabat, Morocco), 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Nour, Queen (Jordan), 1992-1996 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Romare, Kristian, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Students: responses to exhibitions and programs, 1994-1997 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Takla, Leila (Cairo), 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Wijdan Ali, Princess (Jordan), 1991-1999 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Events and organizations, 1991-2007
    - Agnes Scott College (Decatur, GA), "Right to Write" exhibition, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Al Qattan Foundation (Palestine): Young Artists Jury Award, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - American Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - American Arts Festival (Amman, Jordan), 1996-1998 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - American Association of University Women, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - American University of Beirut Alumni Association, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Arab American National Museum (Dearborn, MI), 2001-2007 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Arab American University Graduates, Association of (AAUG), 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Arab Cultural Center (San Francisco), 1991-2002 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Arab Resource Center for the Arts (Beirut), 1994-2002 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Arc Collective (Bay Area Arab Artists Collective), 2004-2007 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Art in Embassies Program, U.S. Department of State (Amman, Jordan), 1998-1999 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Bassira group (Amman, Jordan), 1997 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Canadian Museum of Civilization (Hull, QC), 1995-2001 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Darat al Funun (Amman, Jordan), 1994-2001 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - "Displacement and Difference," London Middle East Institute (SOAS), 1999 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco (Eternal Egypt exhibition), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Ford Foundation (state of Arab American Cultural Organizations), 2001 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Middle East Public Policy Council (Washington), 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Programs, Los Angeles, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Speaking engagements, Bay Area, 1991-2007 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Speaking engagements, general, 1992-2006 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Symposium, "Women Creators of the Mediterranean" (Rhodes, Greece), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - World Affairs Council of Northern California, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Permissions, 1994-2005
    - Arab Cultural Festival (San Francisco), 1999 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Arab Media House (Arlington, VA), 1994 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Cune (literary magazine, Seattle), 1997-1999 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - General, 1995-2000 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Georgetown University, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Graywolf Press, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Greenwillow Books (Naomi Nye), 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Interlink Publishers (London), 1999 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - McGraw-Hill, Glencoe Literature textbook (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - National Institute for Technology in Liberal Education (NITLE), 2002 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Ohio Northern University, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Population Council, 1996-1998 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Publishers, various, 1994-2000 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Simon and Schuster, Naomi Nye project, 1996-1998
    - Syracuse Cultural Workers (Syracuse, NY), 1999-2005 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Teachers Curriculum Institute, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - University of Texas Press, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Projects, research, and miscellaneous, 1992-2006
    - Art works: prices at galleries, 1992-1998 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Book publishers: PROTA / Salma Jayyusi, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Book proposals, 1996-1999 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Conferences/Exhibitions: Liminal Spaces (Palestine), 2006 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Dialogue of the Present (Women's Art Library, London): chapter in catalogue, by S. Mikdadi, 1997-1998 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York): Timeline of Art History, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Palestinian Art Court – al Hoash, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - PARC: Palestinian-American Research Center (Villanova University), 2004-2005 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Publications, registration of, 1997-2001 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Writings: "Visitor Voices in Art Museums," by Salwa Mikdadi. Journal of Museum Education, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Resources and subject files, 1989-2004
    - Essays: Adra, Najwa, "Yemen Education Culture Grant," and other writings, 1993-2000 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Essays: Alaoui, Ibrahim (Darat al Funun), "Contemporary Arab Art,", 1996 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Essays: Ali, Wijdan. "What is Islamic Art?" (booklet, Al al-Bayt University), 1996 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Essays: Berlekamp, Persis. "Modernity and Heritage, the Western and Folkloric,", 1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Essays: Chorbachi, Wasma.' "Arab Art Twenty Years Later,", 1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Essays: Khalil, Nadine. "Mapping border crossings and the geographies of hybrid cultures in the diaspora," Thesis proposal, American University Beirut, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Essays: Madkour, Nazli. "Women and Art in Egypt,", 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Essays: Maksoud, Hala. "Women and Change in the Arab World," speech text, World Bank, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Essays: Mudhaffar, May. "Calligraphy in Modern Iraqi Art,", undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - General: articles, essays, related to Arab art and artists, 1994-2002, and undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Museum studies: Condition reports, 2003, and undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Museum studies: Deaccessioning, 1992, and undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Museum studies: Description of artifacts, 1999, and undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Museum studies: General, 1995-2003 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Museum studies: Teacher resources, 1995-2001, and undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Museums: Jordan, 1998, and undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Museums: Lebanon, 1995-1998 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Museums: Middle East and North Africa, general, 1985-2004, and undated (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Museums: Palestine (West Bank), 1995-2000, and undated (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Subject: Calligraphy (al Wasiti), undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Exhibitions, 1989-2009; 5.0 Linear Feet in 12 boxes.
  - Forces of Change: general
    - Arabic text, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Art works, checklists of (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Artists, lists of (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Embassies, Arab (U.S.A.) (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: General, 1991-1994 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Press (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Crate lists / shipping (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Curator's statements (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Documentary video: Correspondence, production (Zuhair al Faqih) (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Documentary video: Scripts (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Educational programming (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Exhibition Advisory Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Films (to be screened in exhibition), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising, general, 1992-1995 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Fundraising: Middle East Institute (Washington, DC): U.S. Outreach Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Fundraising: National Endowment for the Arts (grant application), 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Houston: proposed venue (not realized) (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Loan Agreements (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Loan extensions (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Photographs
    - Press releases, Arabic (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Press coverage (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Proposals, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Public relations, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Publicity: segment on NPR's All Things Considered, February 27, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - South American venues (proposed), 1993-1996 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Translations of texts (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Venues contacted (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Wall labels (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Forces of Change: Atlanta
    - Arab American Womens Society of Georgia, folder 1 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Arab American Womens Society of Georgia, folder 2 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Educational programming (children) (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Evaluations from docents (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Guest books/visitor registers, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Gwinett Fine Arts Center (exhibition venue) (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Nexus Contemporary Arts Center (exhibition venue) (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Press coverage (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Publicity (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Symposium, Emory University / Carter Center (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Forces of Change: Chicago
    - Artists' visits (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Brochures and invitations (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Committee—Fundraising (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Committee—Members (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Committee—Planning (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Contract (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Design, of exhibition (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Educational programming and events (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Guest books/visitor registers, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Installation and deinstallation (Michael Biddle) (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Press coverage (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Public relations: correspondence (Susan Longworth) (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Public relations: materials (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Publicity (press packet) (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Forces of Change: Miami
    - Arab community (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Brochures (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Contract (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Guest books/visitor registers, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Media: Arab-American (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Media: Pacifica Radio (Barbara Nimri Aziz), 1994 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Press coverage (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Forces of Change: Walnut Creek, CA
    - Contract (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, gallery (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Docent workshop (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Fundraising (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Guest books/visitor registers, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Press coverage (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Publicity (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Forces of Change: Washington, DC
    - Adminstrator (R. Abbott) (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Brochure design (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Contract (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Docent training (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Education—Family Day (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising (reception with Queen Noor, October 1993) (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Grace. L. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Guest books/visitor registers, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Library (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1994-1996 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Opening reception/gala (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Press coverage (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Proposal and budget (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Publications (catalogue) (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Publicity (press packet) (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Receptions, private (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Registrar (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Symposium: general (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Symposium: Princess Wijdan Ali, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Rhythm and Form: general
    - Catalogue (both editions) (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: artists and poets (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Loan agreements and condition reports, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Poetry selections (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Program for MESA meeting in 1996, with mention of exhibition on one page
    - Proposal (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Research (1), 1995-1997 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Research (2), 1995-1997 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Research: artists (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Research: poetry (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Rhythm and Form: venues
    - Arkansas: Arkansas, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Arkansas: Catalog and Flyers (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Arkansas: Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Arkansas: Press (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Berkeley: Folder 1, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Berkeley: Folder 2, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Berkeley: Guestbook, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Oregon (Williamette University, Salem): Contract, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Oregon (Williamette University, Salem): Correspondence, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Oregon (Williamette University, Salem): Exhibition catalogue and postcard, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Other exhibitions
    - Artists View: The Arab World: Williamette University: artists statements (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Artists View: The Arab World: Willamette University: catalogue and flyers (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Artists View: The Arab World: Willamette University: correspondence (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Artists View: The Arab World: Willamette University: press and public events (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Badrans: A Century of Tradition and Innovation: Palestinian Art Court - al Hoash (East Jerusalem, Palestine), 2002-2007 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - In/Visible: Arab-American National Museum, general media coverage of opening, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - In/Visible: Brochures, gallery guides, postcards (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - In/Visible: Design and installation (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - In/Visible: Press coverage (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - In/Visible: Symposium (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - In/Visible: Arab-American Museum (Dearborn, MI): visitors comments (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - In/Visible: CDs/DVDs of photographs, media coverage (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - World's Women Online: artists biographies, 1998 and undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - World's Women Online: artists release forms, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - World's Women Online: correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Women of the World/Global Women's Project, 1997-2000 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Other exhibitions: not curated by Mikdadi
    - Canada, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Belgium, 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Denmark, 2000-2005 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - France, 2003-2006 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Europe, other, 2000-2008 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Palestine: Al Wasiti Art Center (Jerusalem), 1994-1996 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - United Kingdom, 1999-2007 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - United States, general, 1988-2007 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - United States, California: Euphrat Center, Cupertino, "Beyond Borders", 1992-1994 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - United States, New York: Williamsburg Bridges, Brooklyn, NY, "Palestine 2002" (Box 46, Folder 10)